[
    {
        "index": 1,
        "question":"What is the loneliest of all physics concepts?",
        "answer":["singularity"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 2,
        "question":"What kind of chemical element hates to be a follower?",
        "answer":["lead"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 3,
        "question":"I come as a gas and I get in line with neon. I am also known as the home of a very super person. What am I?",
        "answer":["krypton"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 4,
        "question":"What number do Nickel and Neon make when combined?",
        "answer":["nine", "9"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 5,
        "question":"I can rush, I can be still, I can be hot, I can be cold, I can be hard, I can slip through almost anything. What am I?",
        "answer":["water"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 6,
        "question":"It is impossible for me to be created, and I can never ever be destroyed, I can only change form. What am I?",
        "answer":["energy"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 7,
        "question":"I was once an old massive star and soon I will be a brightly colored gas cloud, but for now I am a massive explosion. What am I called?",
        "answer":["supernova"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 8,
        "question":"I can be good for you, I can be bad, I can be found all over inside and outside your body. What am I?",
        "answer":["bacteria"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 9,
        "question":"I am a hypothetical tunnel, a short cut if you will, of space-time which connects far away regions. I am a what?",
        "answer":["wormhole"]
    },
    
    {
        "index": 10,
        "question":"What periodic element do pyromaniacs love the most?",
        "answer":["arsenic"]
    }
    
]